Guide to the CITYarts Inc. Records 1969-2016 MS 3096
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Project Binders, 1969-2016; 22 Linear feet in 22 cartons
  - Binder #18. Projects 90-105, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 6)
    Project 92: Stepping Stones, mosaic sculpture, 1982, Manhattan. (Documents only, no photos. See binder 17.).
    Project 93: Hebrew Educational Society of Canarsie Mural, 1982, 9502 Seaview Avenue, Brooklyn. (Mostly documents, including a poem, with few photos. See binder 17.)
    Project 95: La Colonizacion, mural, 1982.
    Project 97: East Harlem Mural, 1982, East 103rd Street and Park Avenue.
    Project 98: Avenue X Gravesend Mural, 1982, Citibank, 265 Avenue X, Brooklyn. (Documents only, no photos. See binder 17.)
    Project 99: Marble Hill Senior Center Mural, 1983, 5365 Broadway, Bronx.
    Project 101: Performing Arts Mosaic, 1983, CPE, 1573 Madison Avenue. (Documents only, no photos.)
    Project 102: Central Park East School Mosaic, 1983, CES 90, 1116 Sheridan Avenue, Bronx.
    Project 103: Home Sweet Hollis Home Mural, 1983, 199th Street & Hollis Avenue, Queens.
    Project 104: Pueblo Nuevo, mural, 1983, 14,15,28 Clinton Street.
    Project 105: St. Albans Greatest Hits, mural, underneath the Saint Albans Long Island Railroad subway station, Queens.
  - Binder #19. Projects 106-113, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 6)
    Project 106: The Tree of Life: Through the Golden Years, mural, 1983, Allen Community Senior Citizen Center, 166-01 Linder Blvd., Jamaica, Queens.
    Project 107: We Shall Live and Build Together, mural, 1983, 24 Furman Avenue, Brooklyn. Project 108: Bushwick Mural, 1983, 24 Furman Avenue, Brooklyn.
    Project 109: Nothing on this project here, but see project 102 in binder 18.
    Project 110: Flowering Light, 1984, mural, 303 West 42nd Street.
    Project 111: Inner City, mural, 1984, CES 2, 1363 Fulton Avenue, Bronx.
    Project 112: Generations (also referred to as From One Generation to Another), mural, 1984, Avenue C between 7th and 8th Avenues.
    Project 113: You'd Wish for a Million Free Parking Spaces or, On Second Thought, That You Could Fly, mural, 1984, 2 Steinway Street, Astoria, Queens.
  - Binder #20. Projects 114-120, 1985 (Offsite-box 6)
    Project 114: Roof-top Garden Mural, 1985, Village Nursing Home, 607 Hudson Street. (Documents only, no photos. See binder 22).
    Project 115: Plaza Las Americas, mural, 1985, location unclear.
    Project 116: Swim, mural, 1986, Manhattan.
    Project 117: Human Support (also referred to as Los Sures), mural, 1985, Havemeyer and South 4th Street, Williamsburg.
    Project 118: Broadway Starship, sculpture, 1985, Corporal Lawrence Thompson Park, Staten Island (includes exceptionally extensive documentation of the project).
    Project 119: Roman Garden, mural, 1985, CYO Senior Center, Port Richmond, Staten Island. (Documents only, no photos. See binder 22.)
    Project 120: Jackson Heights Mural, 1985, Dan's Supreme Supermarket, 87th & Northern Blvd., Queens.
  - Binder #21. Projects 121-123, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    Project 121: Pasaje Verde, mural, 1985, Casabe Senior Center of Casabe Houses, 150 East 121st Street.
    Project 122: Carroll Gardens Collage, mural, 1985, P.S. 58, 330 Smith Street, Brooklyn.
    Project 123: Birdhouses, 1985-86, Hong Ning Residence for the Elderly, 51 Norfolk Street.
  - Binder #22. Projects 114, 119, 124, 1985 (Offsite-box 7)
    Project 114: Roof-top Garden Mural, 1985, Village Nursing Home, 607 Hudson Street.
    Project 119: Roman Garden, mural, 1985, CYO Senior Center, Port Richmond, Staten Island. (See binder 20).
    Project 124: Rockaway Seniors, 1985, Rockaway Senior Citizens Center, Queens. (See binder 23.)
  - Binder #23. Projects 124-132, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 7)
    Project 124: Rockaway Seniors, mural, 1985, Rockaway Senior Citizens Center. (Documents only, no photos. See binder 22.)
    Project 125: The Musicians, mural, 1986, 169 Rivington Street. (Documents only, no photos.)
    Project 126: Communion/Temple, mural, 1986, United Nations Plaza.
    Project 127: Come Back to Far Rockaway, mural, 1986, Vanguard Building, Far Rockaway, Queens.
    Project 128: The Music Must Continue, mural, 1986, 177 Stanton Street.
    Project 129: Tango USA, mural, 1986, 37th Avenue & Junction Blvd., Queens.
    Project 130: Puerto Rico Theatre, mural, 1986, Queens.
    Project 131: Festival of Our Lives, mural, 1986, Far Rockaway, Queens. (Fact sheet only, no photos.)
    Project 132: A Salute to Ronald R. McNair, Astronaut, mural, 1986, P.S. 132, 1245 Washington Avenue, Bronx.
  - Binder #24. Projects 135-139, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 8)
    Project 135: Senior Citizens Mural, 1987, Brooklyn.
    Project 136: Geometric Abstractions, mural, 1987, J.H.S. 57, 125 Stuyvesant Avenue, Brooklyn. (See also binder 15.)
    Project 137: Louis Armstrong: The Prevalence of Love, Devotion, and Jazz, mural, 1987, 107-10 Northern Blvd., Queens. (See also binder 15.)
    Project 138: Nothing in the binder for this project.
    Project 139: West Astoria Hieroglyphs, mural, 1988, 12-09 Astoria Blvd., Queens.
  - Binder #25. Projects 140-146, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 8)
    Project 140: Jungle Dream, mural, 1988, P.S. 38, 450 Pacific Street, Brooklyn.
    Project 141: Muneco de Nieve (Snow Man), mural, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic. (Documents only, no photos. See also binder 15.)
    Project 142: Home Run, mural, 1988, 140 Hinsdale Street, Brooklyn.
    Project 143: Washington Houses, mural, 1988, 1775 3rd Avenue.
    Project 144: Multi-generational Project, mural, 1988, Washington Community Center/Union Settlement, 1775 3rd Avenue.
    Project 145: Four Drivers, mural, 1989, 55-58 Queens Midtown Expressway.
    Project 146: Through the Bricks, mural, 1989, J.H.S 51, 350 Fifth Ave., Brooklyn. (See also binder 15.)
  - Binder #26. Various Projects (148, 149, 151-153), 1990 (Offsite-box 8)
    Project 148: Queens, mural, 1990, I.S. 126, 31-35 21st Street, Queens. (See also binder 15.)
    Project 149: P.E.P's Bing-Bong Circus, mural, 1990, P.S. 198, 1700 3rd Avenue. (See also binder 15.)
    Project 151: Stapleton Tower Suites Finalists, sculpture, 1990, Tappen Park, Staten Island.
    Project 152: Past, Present, Future, mural, 1990, Garden, 474 Classon Avenue, Brooklyn.(See also binder 15.)
    Project 153: Save the Earth (or Colors of Music?), mural, 1989-90, Joan of Arc School, 154 West 93rd Street. (See also binder 15.)
  - Binder #27. Project 169: Destiny, 1991 (Offsite-box 8)
    Mural, 817 East 180th Street, Bronx. Documents include announcement, correspondence, and other records concerning creation of the mural.
  - Binder #28. Project 159: Displacement & Replacement in the Bronx: The Path of Domination, 1991 (Offsite-box 8)
    Mural, 2120 Mapes Avenue, Bronx. Documents include correspondence, etc.
  - Binder #29. Project 158: Do the Dance of Life, 1991 (Offsite-box 8)
    Mural, 1904 Union Street, Brooklyn. Documents include those from the Department of Housing Preservation and Development, correspondence, notes, etc.
  - Binder #30. Project 164: The Eagle's Nest, Tree of Life, 1991 (Offsite-box 8)
    Mural, 1879 Clinton Avenue, Bronx. Documents include correspondence, grant information, announcements, poem, questionnaires, etc.
  - Binder #31. Project 166: Esta Casa Que Hemos Hecho (This House That We Have Made), 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, Deacon Juan Santos Plaza, 1965 Vyse Avenue, Bronx. Includes correspondence, flyer, announcements, etc.
  - Binder #32. Project 160: Live in Peace with Yourself First, 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 500 W. 159th Street. Includes press release and other promotional materials.
  - Binder #33. Project 171: Longfellow Mural, 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 1496-1504 Longfellow Avenue, Bronx. Includes articles, correspondence, announcements, and certificate.
  - Binder #34. Project 172: Recycle the Planet, 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 823 Hunts Point Avenue, Bronx. Includes correspondence, workplan, and artist statement.
  - Binder #35. Project 165: Tools of the Trade, 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 509 West 160th Street.
  - Binder #36. Project 167: You Are Here, 1991 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 1815 Davidson Avenue, Bronx. Includes correspondence, certificate, and CITYarts Executive Director profile.
  - Binder #37. Project 175: Aim High, Stop the Violence, 1992 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 1435 University Avenue, Bldg. #15, Bronx. Includes press release, article, artist agreement, and flyer. See related project 176 in binder 43.
  - Binder #38. Project 173: Every Life is Unique/Toda La Vida Es Unica, 1992 (Offsite-box 9)
    Mural, 500 West 134th Street at Amsterdam Avenue. Includes flyer, press release, and correspondence.
  - Binder #39. Project 163: Playground Mural, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, Amsterdam, Avenue and 180th Street. Includes press releases, community announcements/informational sheets, and correspondence.
  - Binder #40. Project 162: Sixth Street Community Center, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, 638 East 6th Street.
  - Binder #41. Project 177: The Elements, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, 1506 Walton Avenue, Bronx. Includes flyers, press release and correspondence.
  - Binder #42. Project 168: Times Square Theatre, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, 219 West 42nd Street. Includes articles, announcements, correspondence, etc. See related project 170 in binder 45.
  - Binder #43. Project 176: To Our Homestead, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, 1476 Shakespeare Avenue, Bldg. #5, Bronx. Includes grant and ceremony information, flyers, artist contract, etc. See related project 175 in binder 37.
  - Binder #44. Project 174: West Harlem Wishes, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, 240 West 116th Street. Includes press release and artist agreement.
  - Binder #45. Project 170: Yesterday & Today, 1992 (Offsite-box 10)
    Mural, Nathan's building, 43rd Street and Broadway. Includes articles, announcements, etc. See related project 176 in binder 43.
  - Binder #46. Project 180: Urban Stories Exhibition, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Marine Midland Bank, 599 Broadway. Includes press release, locations sheet, article, promotional materials, etc.
  - Binder #47. Project 185: A Dream Grows in Red Hook, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Mural, Mr. Natural Building, 212 Wolcott Street, Red Hook, Brooklyn. Includes news article and press release.
  - Binder #48. Project 183: Grant's Tomb Benches Restoration, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Includes documents ranging from 1979-1997, including memos, press release, articles, informational sheet, and a historical publication on the site by the National Park Service and the Department of the Interior. The articles relate to the mosaic benches generally as well as to the criticism and contestation over their presence at the memorial.
  - Binder #49. Project 181: Green Village, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Mural, P.S. 3, 490 Hudson Street. Includes press release, unveiling invitation, program, etc.
  - Binder #50. Project 187: Jacob's Ladder, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Sculpture, Dupont Street Senior Residence, 80 Dupont Street, Brooklyn. Includes press release, etc.
  - Binder #51. New York Botanical Garden Mural #1, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Mural, New York Botanical Garden Ruth Rea Howell Family Garden. Includes press release, article, and correspondence, including a congratulatory letter from U.S. Vice President Al Gore.
  - Binder #52. Project 186: Time Out on Broadway, 1994 (Offsite-box 11)
    Mural, The Healy Building, Broadway between 94th and 95th streets. Includes articles, press releases, flyers, etc.
  - Binder #53. Project 188: Young Minds Build Bridges, 1994 (Offsite-box 12)
    Mural, Rodeph Sholom School and the Family Academy. Includes records from the reception, press release, list of participants in the project, an article, and a pamphlet from the school. See also binder 60.
  - Binder #54. Project 189: Circle of Friends, 1995 (Offsite-box 12)
    Sculptures, 1995, Riverside South Temporary Park, 70th-72nd streets. Includes flyers, articles, and press releases.
  - Binder #55. Project 198, 199: Department of Cultural Affairs (DCA) Restoration, 1995 (Offsite-box 12)
    Includes Broadway Starship, Stapleton Suites, Rockaway Mosaic, Greenpoint Gate.
  - Binder #56. Project 193: Learning in Color, 1995 (Offsite-box 12)
    Mural, P.S. 40, 319 East 19th Street. Includes press release, certificate, etc.
  - Binder #57. Project 192: No More War, 1995 (Offsite-box 13)
    Mural, U.N. School, 24-50 FDR Drive. Includes correspondence, etc.
  - Binder #58. Project 190: Sweet Home, 1995 (Offsite-box 13)
    Mural, Meltzer Tower Senior Apartment Complex, 78 East 1st Street. Includes press release.
  - Binder #59. Project 191: Alice in Wall Street Land (also referred to as Wall Street Mural), 1995 (Offsite-box 13)
    55 Broad Street. Includes budget, articles, press release, drawings, flyer, etc.
  - Binder #60. Project 188: Young Minds Build Bridges (Soho Arts Festival), 1995 (Offsite-box 13)
    Mural, Rodeph Shalom Academy. Includes press release and program. See also binder 53.
  - Binder #61. Project 194: Golden Hands, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 13)
    Sculptures placed across Manhattan during the Soho Arts Festival.
  - Binder #62. Project 200: Genesis, 1996 (Offsite-box 13)
    Stained glass mural, 1996, Genesis Apartments at Union Square, 113 East 13th Street. Includes press release, flyer, invitation, sketches, and notes on the design from the artist.
  - Binder #63. Project 196: Hunts Point Mural, 1996 (Offsite-box 13)
    The Point, 940 Garrison Avenue, Bronx. Includes press release, flyer, etc. Also includes related exhibition of sketches for the mural presented at the Mexican Cultural Institute.
  - Binder #64. Projects 202, 203, 204: Kids for Justice, 1996 (Offsite-box 13)
    Mural, Reach Elementary, Hostos Academy, P.S. 6. Includes correspondence, article, announcement, and lesson plans. Also includes photos and information from the 1996 Shakespeare benefit. Further materials are in the back pocket of the binder including a publication on the artwork of Richard Mock "And Through the Eye Correct the Heart" and more articles. See also binder 69.
  - Binder #65. Project 195: Soho Arts Festival, 1996 (Offsite-box 14)
    Mural, Studio Tours, Manhattan. Includes flyer and press release.
  - Binder #66. Project 197: Tributes to Kusama: Arts Infinity-Net., 1996 (Offsite-box 14)
    Mural, Thompson Street Playground. Includes flyer and press release.
  - Binder #67. Various Projects, 1971-1979 (Offsite-box 14)
    Mostly includes articles and photos of project 10: Grants Tomb Mosaic Bench, 1971-74, 122nd Street & Riverside Drive. Additionally there are some materials concerning projects: Changing Walls, 1973 (fact sheet, articles) and "All that Wall and No Graffiti," 1973 (fact sheet, photographs, articles).
  - Binder #68. Project 243: Spirit of New York, 1989-2002 (Offsite-box 14)
    Materials concerning "Spirit of New York" benefit exhibition curated by CITYarts for 55 Wall Street Restaurant at the Regent Wall Street. The binder includes: fact sheets, exhibition listing, articles, artist statements, artist bios, etc.
  - Binder #69. Projects 202, 203, 204: Kids for Justice, 1996 (Offsite-box 14)
    Mural, Reach Elementary, Hostos Academy, P.S. 6. Includes artist statement, correspondence, articles, announcements, etc. See also binder 64.
  - Binder #70. CityArts/ Joseph Papp Public Theatre Collaboration (Kids for Peace), 1997 (Offsite-box 14)
    Includes various documents. There is also an unrelated fact sheet on a CITYarts and New York City Kids Ceremony to Honor Kareem Abdul-Jabbar (1997, The Museum for African Art, 593 Broadway).
  - Binder #71. Comite D' Accueil Canada-France, 1997 (Offsite-box 14)
    Temporary canvas paintings, P.S. 1, 8 Henry Street between Catherine and Oliver streets. Includes announcement.
  - Binder #72. Project 206: Dreams of Home, 1997 (Offsite-box 14)
    Mural, Visy Paper Mill, 4435 Victory Blvd., Staten Island. Includes credit line, press releases, project schedule, etc.
  - Binder #73. Project 205: Flowering Vine, 1997 (Offsite-box 15)
    Mural, St. James Square Park. Includes artist statement, two 3-1/2 inch floppy disks of digital content for related postcard, etc.
  - Binder #74. Kids For Justice (binder 1 of 2), 1997 (Offsite-box 15)
    Kids for Justice Traveling Exhibition, 1997, related to projects 202, 203 and 204, The Scholastic Gallery at 555 Broadway. The binder includes a program fact sheet, flyer, invitation, announcement, press release, correspondence, program information, etc.
  - Binder #75. Kids For Justice (binder 2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 15)
    Related to Kids for Justice projects 207 and 209, 1997-98. Includes press release, correspondence, promotional materials, etc.
  - Binder #76. Projects 214-223: Kids for Peace: A World in Harmony, 1998 (Offsite-box 15)
    Murals, 1998-99, Simon Baruch School, Clinton School, Dwight School, Crossroads School, Friends Seminary, Haywood-Burns School, I.S. 131, Rodeph Sholom School, and La Scoula Guglielmo Marconi School. This binder includes both photographs and records from several of these projects.
  - Binder #77. Project 212: Kids for Justice: The Pillars of Justice (binder 1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 15)
    Mural, Simon Baruch Middle School, 330 East 21st Street.
  - Binder #78. Project 212: Kids for Justice: The Pillars of Justice (binder 2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 15)
    Mural, Simon Baruch Middle School, 330 East 21st Street. Includes press release, correspondence, lesson plan, etc.
  - Binder #79. Project 211: A Congo Chronicle: Patrice Lumumba in Urban Art, 1999 (Offsite-box 15)
    Mural, Museum for African Art. Includes flyer and article.
  - Binder #80. Projects 214-223: Kids for Peace, 1999 (Offsite-box 16)
    Murals, various locations. Includes Kids for Peace participant certificate and flyer/invitation, correspondence, and sketches, Also, folder with records from Celebrating the Heroes of Our City.
  - Binder #81. Project 227: Banana Republic Exhibition, 2000 (Offsite-box 16)
    Project 227: Public Art Exhibition and benefit at Banana Republic, 2000, 59th Street and Lexington Avenue location (includes programs).
  - Binder #82. Project 236: Cultural Mosaic, 2000 (Offsite-box 16)
    Mural, 210 West 146th Street. Includes program, artist contract, correspondence, invitation to dedication, statement from the artist, etc.
  - Binder #83. Project 230: Living on Mars (binder 1 of 2), 2000 (Offsite-box 16)
    Mural, Schoolyard Wall, C.E.S. (Community Elementary School) 64, Walton Avenue, Bronx. Includes invitation, correspondence (including with First Lady Hillary Clinton), announcement, press release, article, publication by the Planetary Society, records from the ceremony, teacher's guide concerning the topic, etc.
  - Binder #84. Project 230: Living on Mars (binder 2 of 2), 2000 (Offsite-box 16)
  - Binder #85. Project 237: Rivers of Communication (binder 1 of 3), 2000 (Offsite-box 17)
    Mural, Grand Canal Court, Avenue of the Americas and Thompson Street. Includes certificate of accomplishment, pamphlet of art by Osmo Rauhala, correspondence, press release, article, etc.
  - Binder #86. Project 237: Rivers of Communication (binder 2 of 3). Slides and negatives), 2000 (Offsite-box 17)
  - Binder #87. Project 237: Rivers of Communication (binder 3 of 3). Ribbon Cutting Ceremony), 2000 (Offsite-box 17)
  - Binder #88. Project 228: Wishes to Mars (binder 1 of 2), 2000-2003 (Offsite-box 17)
    Sculpture, CES (Community Elementary School) 64, Bronx. Includes media alerts, notes, pamphlet about the program, etc.
  - Binder #89. Project 228: Wishes to Mars (binder 2 of 2), 2000-2003 (Offsite-box 17)
  - Binder #90. Small Projects, 2001-2003 (Offsite-box 19)
    Various materials concerning: Project 229 (St. Alban's Restoration Mural, 2001, The St. Alban's School); Chashama Theatre-Urban Arts Festival (2003, Chashama Theatre, 135 West 42nd Street); The Many Faces of NY projects; Project 249 (Starbucks on 38 Park Row, 2002).
  - Binder #91. Project 242: Forever Tall, 2001 (Offsite-box 17)
    Mural, 35 Cooper Square. Includes press release, correspondence, article, etc.
  - Binder #92. Project 241: Living Sculpture, 2001 (Offsite-box 19)
    Floyd Bennet Field Gardens, Brooklyn. Includes flyers, announcement, press release, etc.
  - Binder #93. Project 246: Celebrating the Heroes of our City (binder 1 of 4), 2002 (Offsite-box 18)
    Mural, Henry M. Jackson Playground, intersection of Henry, Grand & Madison streets. Binders include many documents, such as certificate, flyers, permit, articles, correspondence, CDs with digital content.
  - Binder #94. Project 246: Celebrating the Heroes of our City (binder 2 of 4), 2002 (Offsite-box 18)
    Project 246. Celebrating the Heroes of Our City, 2002, Henry M. Jackson Playground, intersection of Henry, Grand & Madison streets (includes a CD).
  - Binder #95: Project 246: Celebrating the Heroes of our City (binder 3 of 4), 2002 (Offsite-box 18)
    Project 246. Celebrating the Heroes of Our City, 2002, Henry M. Jackson Playground, intersection of Henry, Grand & Madison streets (fact sheet, certificate, flyer, permit, article, correspondence).
  - Binder #96: Project 246: Celebrating the Heroes of our City (binder 4 of 4), 2002 (Offsite-box 18)
    Project 246. Celebrating the Heroes of Our City, 2002, Henry M. Jackson Playground, intersection of Henry, Grand & Madison streets (includes CD, announcement flyers, certificate, and a magazine-like publication on the project).
  - Binder #97. Project 226: Kids for Justice. Pillars of Justice, 2000 (Offsite-box 18)
  - Binder #98. Project 251: Discovery of Dreams, 2003 (Offsite-box 18)
    Mural, P.S. 193, Queens. Includes correspondence, press release, etc.
  - Binder #99. Project 253: Sundial, 2004 (Offsite-box 18)
    Sculpture, P.S. 72., 104th Street and Lexington Avenue. Includes notes, 6 CDs, a program, etc.
  - Binder #100. Project 265: Reaching for the Stars, 2006 (Offsite-box 19)
    Mural, Washington Irving High School, 40 Irving Place. Includes flyer, invitation, press releases, article, and 8 CDs.
  - Binder #101. Project 266: Safe Spaces, 2006 (Offsite-box 19)
    Mural, Claremont Pool, East 170th Street, Bronx. Includes correspondence, children's drawings and 5 CDs.
  - Binder #102. Project 263: Welcome to our Neighborhood, 2006 (Offsite-box 19)
    Mural, NY Department of Homeless Services Intake Center, 346 Powers Avenue, Bronx. Includes press release, media advisory, other press records, artist bio, final report flyers, members list, certificate, and 3 CDs.
  - Binder #103. City Arts Projects, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 19)
    Materials from various projects in the programs Engaging Graffiti Kids in Creation, not Destruction (projects 266 and 268) and Commmunity Identity (project 265). The binder includes timelines, calendars, project updates, ribbon cutting ceremony schedule, press release, map, 6 CDs, contact sheet, budgets, proposals, site information, sketches, site photographs, etc.
  - Binder #104. Project 268: Heat Dances to the Sun's Beat, 2007 (Offsite-box 19)
    Mural, Baruch Park at corner of Stanton and Mangin streets. Includes general overview, 5 CDs, flyers, correspondence, artist statement, and press releases.
  - Binder #105. Project 246?: The Wildlife Mosaic: The Tile Project, 2002 (Offsite-box 19)
    Mosaic, 14 East 33rd Street.
  - Binder. Against Domestic Colonialism (restoration), 1972, 1973, 2011 (Offsite-box 20)
    Restoration of Project 9: Against Domestic Colonialism, 1972, 430 West 46th Street. Includes articles.
  - Binder. Project 178: The Nature of This Flower is to Bloom, 1993 (Offsite-box 20)
    Mural, Pintchik Decorating Center (as of 2021, a Petco), 92nd Street & Broadway. Includes press releases, artist statement, sketches.